export const frageAntwort = [
	{
		question: "1: ____ is my favourite tank in Final Fantasy XIV!",
		options: ["Paladin", "Warrior", "Dark Knight", "Gunbreaker"],
		answer: 3,
	},

	{
		question: "2: My favourite DPS has to be ____",
		options: ["Ninja", "Samurai", "Viper", "Black Mage"],
		answer: 2,
	},
	{
		question:
			"3: Which uncconventional pizza topping do i crown as the best?",
		options: [
			"Apples, bacon, caramelised onions and cheddar",
			"Broccoli, corn and hollandaise sauce",
			"Kebab Pizza",
			"Schnitzel stripes, red onions, hollandaise sauce and broccoli",
		],
		answer: 1,
	},
	{
		question: "4: My green spirit animal:",
		options: [
			"Borpa",
			"Dat Boi (the frog on the unicycle xD)",
			"Glorpcat",
			"Pepe (or Peepo)",
		],
		answer: [0, 2],
	},
	{
		question: "5: There is ... inside of me.",
		options: [
			"a wolf",
			"a pair of wolves who are both gay",
			"an ice fairy",
			"a skeleton that tries to take control",
			"a skeleton that already took control",
			"nothing",
		],
		answer: [2, 3],
	},
	{
		question: "6.1: I think I'm ...",
		options: [
			"Gojo (Jujutsu Kaisen)",
			"Escanor (Seven Deadly Sins)",
			"Lelouch (Code Geass)",
			"Michael Kaiser (Blue Lock)",
		],
		answer: [0, 3],
	},
	{
		question: "6.2: ...but realistically I'm...",
		options: [
			"Deku's Mom (Boku no Hero Academia)",
			"Griffith (Berserk)",
			"Lain (Serial Experiments Lain)",
			"Shinji (Evangelion)",
		],
		answer: 3,
	},
	{
		question: "7: I hear/watch this when I want to laugh:",
		options: [
			"5 Minuten Harry Podcast",
			"Brooklyn 99",
			"Hobbylos",
			"The Office",
			"Quin69",
		],
		answer: [2, 4],
	},
	{
		question: "8: I grew up playing lots of...",
		options: [
			"Jak and Daxter",
			"Magic: The Gathering",
			"Street Fighter",
			"Zelda",
		],
		answer: 3,
	},
	{
		question:
			"9: An anime I like but saying it out loud is like asking for a ticket to jail:",
		options: [
			"Boku no Pico",
			"Kissxsis",
			"Oreimo",
			"School Days",
			"Yosuga no Sora",
		],
		answer: 1,
	},
	{
		question: "10: My favourite Final Fantasy Protagonist is...",
		options: ["Cloud", "Lightning", "Tidus", "Vaan"],
		answer: 2,
	},
	{
		question:
			"11: The coolest maincharacter-persona in the Persona series (I never played P1 and P2):",
		options: ["Orpheus", "Thanatos", "Izanagi", "Ars√®ne"],
		answer: 2,
	},
	{
		question: "12: The question is simple:",
		options: ["Asuka", "Rei"],
		answer: 0,
	},
	{
		question: "13: This question is simple aswell:",
		options: ["Aerith", "Barret", "Tifa", "Yuffie"],
		answer: 3,
	},
	{
		question: "14: This guy does the coolest content on YouTube",
		options: [
			"Abroad in Japan",
			"KBash",
			"PrimeAgen",
			"Super Eyepatch Wolf",
		],
		answer: 3,
	},
];
